# HIKARI KOBE

# Front-End Developer

(778)840-1785 | Marie h.kobe712@gmail.com | Vancouver, BC | Hikari7 | Portfolio | In hikari-kobe

#### SUMMARY

As a specialized Front-End Developer with expertise in React, I am dedicated to creating user-friendly websites utilizing my proficiency in CSS and React. With 3 years of experience as a technical support specialist in customer service, I possess exceptional communication skills and the ability to collaborate effectively with team members. Seeking a position in a team environment to further hone my skills as a Front-End Developer.

#### SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks, Libraries, and Environments: React, Redux, React Router, Sass, Bootstrap, Material UI,

Styled-component, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Gatsby, Next.js, Node.js

Others: Firebase, MongoDB, Git, Figma

# **PROJECTS**

Appointly (React, MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, Redux, Tailwind.css)

A team project to create and share customizable calendar availability with others, enabling them to book appointments, meetings, and events at pre-scheduled times.

MERN Note App(React, MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, Redux, Material UI)

Implemented user authentication using JWT and enabled features such as note creation, editing, deletion, and post liking.

Workout Tracker (React, Material UI, Firebase)

A workout tracker recording app provides the store the user information and their posts. Manipulating data with Firebase.

Sleep tight (React, GSAP, Tailwind CSS, Youtube Data API v3)

A web app only plays BGM-related relaxing sounds fetched by Youtube Data API. Well designed the minimized styling to help the user to focus on sleeping.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer/Designer Assistant | Easy Technology k.k | Japan | 2023.4 - Present

- Worked as a front-end developer for a Fintech start-up company focused on creating software for debt collections, using TypeScript and Next.js to build robust and user-friendly interfaces.
- · Collaborated with the designer to implement their vision, using Figma to ensure a seamless design-todevelopment process.

Frontend Developer/Designer (Freelance) | Vancouver, BC | 2022.5 - Present

## Live streaming service

Experienced in design and UI engineering for a live streaming service startup company

Skilled in front-end development using React and Chakra UI

## Second-hand Book E-commerce Site

Collaborated with a startup company based in Nigeria to deliver the project

- · Contributed to the design and development of the site as a front-end Developer
- Improved user experience and aesthetic appeal of the site by working on the front-end

Technical Support Specialist / Trainer, Japan Concentrix k.k | Japan | 2019.5 - 2022.2

- · Offered various customer technical support ranging from supporting the launch of a hotel property's website on the online travel agency site and to game player technical support.
- · Trained more than 130 employees successfully and received the Best Employee of the Quarter Award for my training achievements.

#### **EDUCATION**

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada | Vancouver, BC | 2022.5 - Present

Web and Mobile Application Development Diploma

Seinan Gakuin University | Japan | 2014.4 - 2018.3

Bachelor of Intercultural studies